# RILEY MCGOWEN

mcgowenriley@gmail.com
(206) 257-8125
https://www.linkedin.com/in/riley-mcgowen/

### **CAREER OBJECTIVES**

It is my goal to keep growing my knowledge and experience within the tech-field. I see myself in the near-future exploring more avenues for desktop support, and working with more operating systems to grow my ability to provide the best support. Helping large and small companies run as effectively and efficiently as possible.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### PillPack – IT Support Associate II – June 2020 – August 2020

- Have taken HIPAA training since PillPack is a pharmacy
- Provided support and/or administrated: Windows & Mac devices, Google Suite, Office 365, Active Directory, Amazon Workspaces, Amazon Chime, Slack, Okta, Five9 phone tool, remote access tools

### American Farms Consulting – IT Technician / Security Compliance – June 2019 – February 2020

- Assist with purchasing of IT hardware
- Setup and maintenance of IP cameras and NVR's spanning 9 different locations
- Printer server installation and maintenance with Windows environments
- Desktop support for Windows computers
- Adhering to RCW and WAC security regulations
- Installation & maintenance of AirMAX and UniFi equipment
- Access Point setup for large outdoor properties
- Cat 5e/6 wiring for indoor/outdoor runs

### Ancient Mountain Treasures – Interim Social Media / Web Admin – December 2018 – February 2020

- Set up Google Analytics for social media and Shopify store
- Shipping/receiving of gems and minerals
- Customer support via social media
- Installation of Shopify plugins for site functionality and marketing
- General IT work

### **Self-employed – Server Administrator** – October 2018 – November 2018

- Linux dedicated server hosting for website build
- Setup and configuration of LAMP web-server
- Building of WordPress website

#### ZoomHash, LLC. – June 2015 – October 2018

### **Assistant Operations Manager / Sales**

- Management of 12+ employees
- Scheduling of technicians to ensure smooth operations
- Setting up appointments with new prospects or clients
- Acquiring and accommodating new clients from online marketing
- Assist CEO & Director with operations management and office administration
- Receiving, scanning, and relaying of legal documents and other forms
- Present performance reports for employees under my management
- Assist CPA with accounts payable & receivable on Bill.com
- Order supplies for office and technical operations
- B2B and B2C sales, with small number of multi-million-dollar clients

## **Site Supervisor**

- Technical/customer support for investors/customers
- Purchasing equipment and hardware for customers and the company
- Inventory management for customer & company assets
- Assisting with performance reviews
- Keeping the team working efficiently and diligently
- Lead role in emergency response situations
- Assisting with the scheduling of employees
- Ensuring effective team collaboration
- Training and working with technicians

### Senior Lead Technician

- Administration and maintenance of client hardware & software
- Managing network with over 2000+ machines
- Lead deployments of customer's hardware & software with team of technicians
- Handle & process returns/RMA for customer's
- Technical/customer support for investors/customers
- Management of Linux & Windows machines including cryptocurrency miners
- Balancing 3-phase & single phase PDUs
- Team training for technicians on maintenance of Linux & Windows machines
- Emergency response (24/7 on call)
- Racking, IP assignment via MAC address, and server configuration

## **Computer Technician**

- Administrate and maintain Linux & Windows machines
- Assess and repair/replace computer hardware
- Installation and administration of cryptocurrency mining software
- Customer support with clients owning 2000+ machines
- Racking, IP assignment via MAC address, and server configuration

### **SKILLS**

- Operations management
- Technical troubleshooting & support
- Windows & Linux system administration
- Software & hardware deployment (racking, configuration, etc.)
- Cryptocurrency mining operations
- Ticketing systems (e.g. Zendesk)
- Emergency response (24/7 on call)
- Executive and upper-level management assistance
- Office administration
- Accounts payable & receivable assistance (Bill.com)
- Supervising of technicians
- WordPress website building
- Photoshop
- Shopify store management
- Social media marketing
- 91 wpm typing speed

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Came into ZoomHash with a running start of technical expertise
- 70% salary increase, within 3.5 years of working with three promotions
- Assisted executives
- Was promoted to a managerial role at the age of 22 with my own office
- Managed three facilities consisting of 8-megawatts of power in total
- Received recommendation from initial ownership of ZoomHash on LinkedIn (Jared R.)

### **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma - Insight School of Washington

#### RECOMMENDATIONS

**Jared Richardson:** "Riley McGowen is a highly capable and responsible individual. At a younger age than many could have done so, he managed groups of people and multiple priorities and projects as well as some degree of customer relationships. He would be an asset to any organization, big or small." – As per LinkedIn

**Connor Bangasser:** "Riley proved to be a very strong hands on and involved supervisor. Very helpful when anyone needed assistance fixing deep hardware issues and was more proficient with troubleshooting skills across multiple job sites. Was a pleasure working with him while I did. Would be a great addition to any team."

- As per LinkedIn

### **REFERENCES**

**Myron Katsapas** – Executive at American Farms Consulting (509) 679-2328

**Jared Richardson** – Former Executive at ZoomHash (714) 599-1974

**Shad Harlan** – Former Supervisor at ZoomHash (509) 860-6776

**Keith Beason** – Former colleague from PillPack (937) 475-8525